<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Analysis II on USP 654 Fall 2017</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Analysis II on USP 654 Fall 2017</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Note: The schedule of topics and assignments might be subject to change.  Date Lesson Reading Assignment Lecture Lab    Part 1: Introduction &amp;amp; Data Analysis Workflow       09/25 Introduction and Data Analysis Workflow        Part 2: Linear Regression       10/02 Bivariate Regression       10/09 DEADLINE: Project proposal       10/09 Multiple Regression (1)       10/16 Multiple Regression (2)       10/23 Dummy Variables       10/30 Interactions       11/06 Non-Linear Relationship, Indirect Effects and Omitted Variable Bias       11/13 DEADLINE: Project update       11/13 Outliers, Heteroskedasticity, and Multicollinearity       11/17 DEADLINE: Assignment 2        Part 3: Generalized Linear Models       11/20 Generalized Linear Models I       11/27 Generalized Linear Models; Where to go next       12/4 DEADLINE: Project Presentation       12/8 DEADLINE: Project Report       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policies</title>
      <link>/policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/policies/</guid>
      <description>Grading: 3 homework assignments and the class project+paper will make up your entire grade in the course. I use these grading cutoffs:
 A=90% B=80% C=70% D=60% F&amp;lt;60%  Notes  If my office hours conflict with your schedule, send me a Google calendar invite for an appointment. Submit in your homework assignments to D2L/Assignments. Extensions on homework due dates will only be granted in exceptional circumstances and only if I am contacted before the due date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools &amp; Datasets</title>
      <link>/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tools/</guid>
      <description>Tools R + RStudio R is the statistical programming language we will use in this class. We will interface with R using RStudio, a fully feautred IDE. Installing them on your own computer should be straightforward. If you already have them installed on your computer, I recommend you check the version and upgrade them to the latest version. Ask me for help if you have any problem installing them.
 Download and install R 3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>